Guide to the Burton Hall Papers WAG.087
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Union Democracy Cases
  - Subseries E: Entertainment
    - American Federation of Musicians (AFM)
      - Stipulation & Notice to Take Depositions, Jan 1, 1972; Pre Trial Examination, Mar 3, 1972; Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, BH; Trial Memorandum, Plaintiff; Case Discontinued, Oct 8, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Local 802 Orphan folder; Fabowitz, Milton v. Local 802, 1964; Janell, Carl - NLRB, 1966; Elkin, Leo - Radio City Music Hall, 1979, 1964-1979 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Rank & File Documents - Correspondence, Publications, Platform, Resolutions, 1958-1969 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Operators (IATSE)
      - Feltington, Dennis v. IATSE, Local 306, 77 Civ. 4417; Index; LRRM Summary with 1987 Memorandum & Decision; Letter of Expulsion, Nov 8, 1977; Questions for the Trial Committee, 1977, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - NLRB Charge, Deposition, D. Feltington, Feb 11 1977; Police Report, Criminal Trespass, May 10, 1977; Trial Transcript (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Report of Executive Board, May 31, 1977; Motion for Preliminary Injunction, Sept, 1977;Answer, Defendants (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Summons, Sept 7 1977; Affidavits in Opposition to Motion for Preliminary injunction (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Stipulation, Sept 29 1977; Correspondence, Dec 28, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Endorsement, Jan 10 1978, Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 1- 189, Mar 20, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 190-345, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Plaintiff's Memorandum on Issue of Trial Committee's Bias; Deposition, Abraham Friedman, Deposition, Alex Popkin, May 19, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 1-100, May 19, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 101-175, May 19, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Deposition, D. Feltington, pp. 177-232, May 21, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Magistrate's PreTrial Order May 26 1978; Court Hearing; PreTrial Order Je 5 1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence July 7 1978; Affirmation Aug 1 1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Plaintiff on Demand for Jury Trial; Correspondence Dec 23 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Voir Dire of Prospective Jurors; Notice of Motion Dec 21 1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Docket No. 78-7583 Feltington; Court Papers, Jan 2, 1979; Court OrderJuly 18 1979; Order to Show Cause, July 23, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Affidavit (D. Feltington), July 23, 1979; Court Order, Aug, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Petition for Leave to Appeal; Petition for Rehearing; Correspondence, Feb 22, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Court Appearance before Judge Goettel, Feb 22, 1980; Notice of Appeal, Mar 25, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Notice of Motion, Mar 31, 1980; Correspondence (with Attachment) Jan 5, 1983, 1980, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Appellate Briefs; Petition for ReHearing, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Joint Appendix (78-7583), undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Docket No. 80-7261 Appellate Briefs; Joint Appendix, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - 85 Civ. 0303; Correspondence (BH) Apr 7 1987; Notice of Cross- Motion, Je 30, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - 77 Civ. 4417 / 85 Civ. 0303; Correspondence, July 6, 1987; Correspondence, Jan 2, 1990, 1987, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Constitution, By-Laws, Local 306; Trial Transcript; Removal from Union Office (with Map), undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Fine v Feltington, Picket Line Assault Charges, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET)
      - Plimack, H. v. NABET & Local 16 (& ABC), 84 Civ 0142 (LBS), (U.S.D.J. Leonard B. Sands) Arbitration Opinion and Award, Aug 3, 1983; Summons and Complaint; Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Preliminary Injunction (BH) (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Plaintiff's Memorandum in Opposition to Defendant's Motion for Summary Judgment; Order - Judge Sands; Correspondence, Apr 4, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - 85 Civ. 4668 (LBS) Plimack (Continuance); Complaint (2nd), Je 14, 1985; Plaintiff's 1st Interrogatories, Dec 9, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Affidavit, H. Plimack Jan 6, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, President, Local 16, Feb 5, 1986, pp. 1- 118 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, pp. 119-223, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, pp. 224-290, Feb 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Deposition, J. Nolan, pp. 291-355; Deposition of W. Lloyd, pp. 1-46, Feb 28, 1986 (with Attachments) (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Deposition, H. Plimack,; pp. 1-186A, Mar 18, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Apr 21, 1986; Affidavit, Howard Atlas, Region 1 Vice-President, NABET, Oct 30, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Notice of Motion for Defendants' Summary Judgment & Dismissing Plaintiff's Complaint, Nov 7, 1986; Reply & Answering Affidavit, J. Nolan, Dec 17, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Reply Affidavit, W. Sloan, Jan 14 1987; Decision, Judge Sands; Correspondence, W. Sloan, Apr 27, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Constitution, By-Laws Oct 14 1982, LM-2s (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Election Correspondence Oct 26 1978; "Dear NABET Brothers & Sisters," Aug 16, 1983, 1978, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Correspondence, Aug 18, 1983; Correspondence, Mar 12, 1985, 1983, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Trial Transcript, Dec 7, 1984; Correspondence, J. Nolan; Transcript (Select Pages) (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Executive Board, Membership Meeting Minutes, with Notes, Dec 6, 1976 - Dec 19 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Executive Board, Membership Meeting Minutes, with Notes, Feb 13 1980 - Feb 28 1986, 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Undated Meeting Minutes, Notes, Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Subseries F: Garment Workers - International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU)
    - Putterman v. Knitgoods Workers; Local 155, ILGWU, 78 Civ. 6000 (MJL); Deposition, V. Putterman, pp. 1-118, Feb 21, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Deposition, V. Putterman, pp. 119-253, Feb 28, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Deposition, V. Putterman, pp. 254-386, Feb 28, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Deposition, Sol C. Chaikin, pp. 1-74, Sept 12, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Deposition, Sol Greene, pp. 1-82, Nov 12, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Deposition, Norman Lewis, pp. 1-41, Dec 5, 1979, Willard Aldrich, pp. 1-43, Dec 5, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Deposition, Salvatore De Angelis, pp. 1-169, Jan 8, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - The Cutters Independent Club; Proposals for Election Procedure, Jan 18, 1968; Correspondence, BH, Dec 18, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Complaint; Plaintiffs' Sur-Reply Memorandum, Jan 2, 1969; Plaintiff's Statement under Rule 9(g), Dec 20, 1969; Defendant's Reply Memorandum, Ravaschieri, Louis v. George P. Schultz, Secretary, Department of Labor (Failure to Enforce Title IV), 76 Civ. 3204, Dec 30, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Election Complaint, Jan 15, 1974; C.B. Motley, D.J., Memorandum & Opinion, 76 Civ. 3204, Mar 17, 1976, 1974, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Rosario, Tomas, Vega, Ovidio, & Cabel, Raymond v. Abe Dolgen, Manager, Local 10, & ILGWU, 69 Civ. 2958; Correspondence, T. Rosario to Local 10, Jan 21, 1970; Correspondence, BH, Aug 28, 1972, 1970, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Docket No. 76 - 7472, Rosario Appellees' Brief (BH), Defendants-Appellants' Brief, Oct 15, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Court Appearance, May 13 1977; Memorandum Opinion, C.B. Motley, pp. 1-60, Nov 14, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - 75 Civ. 4632 (CBM) / 75 Civ. 3204 (CBM); Deposition, T. Rosario,; pp. 1-150,Feb 13, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - 76 Civ. 3204 (CBM); Deposition, T. Rosario, pp. 151-301, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Deposition, T. Rosario, pp. 302-542, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Deposition, T. Rosario, pp. 1-112, Mar 8, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Pre-Trial examination, Vega, Ovidio, pp. 2-149, with Correspondence, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Deposition, Cabel, Raymond E., pp. 1-186, Feb 21, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Pre-Trial Examination, R. Cabel, pp. 1-39, Mar 9, 1978; Pre-Trial Examination, Achu, Beraidin, pp. 1-37, Mar 31, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - 76 Civ. 3204 / 75 civ. 4632; Transcripts (Partial), undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - 78-7335; Appellate Briefs - Defendants, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Appellate Brief - Plaintiffs; Petition for ReHearing (BH), undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - 78-7335-37; Reply Briefs of Defendant-Appellants, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Joint Appendix, Vol. 1 of 2, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Joint Appendix, Vol. 2; 78-7335-37, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Petition for a Writ of Certiorari, Oct, 1979; Brief in Opposition, Local 10 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Deposition, B. Hall, Feb 1, 1982; 76 Civ. 3204 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - 75 Civ. 4632; Correspondence to Vincent P. Broderick, D.J., Je 6, 1983; Court Appearance, Transcript; Application for Fee Award, Apr 26, 1984, 1983, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - 84-7469 / 7491; Decision, U.S. Court of Appeals, Aug, 1984; Appellate Briefs; Reply Briefs; Joint Appendix (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Louis Mendola, Aronoff, Morris, Rodriquez, Pablo, Lascher, Jacob, Intra-union Charges, Local 10, NLRB, Correspondence, Aug 12, 1969; ILGWU Retirement Fund, Correspondence, Nov, 1978, 1969, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - David Spitzer, Local 10, Resolution on Legal Defense Fees for Abe Dolgen, LM-2, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Department of Labor/ILGWU, ILGWU Loans, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - The Cutters Club Documents, Local 10 (Copies), undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Original Documents, Cutters Club, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - F.O.U.R. / Chuck Lang, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - F.O.U.R. Newsletters, News Articles on F.O.U.R., undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Original Papers on Staff Union Organizing, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Industry Critiques/ILGWU; Newspaper & Magazine Clippings, "For the Record" - Justice; Response to NAACP; Reports, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - ILGWU Documents (International), undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Subseries G: Hospital Workers - District 1199, National Union of Hospital & Health Care Employees - Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Union (RWDSU)
    - Brown, Mattie v Nicholas, Henry, President, 82 Civ. 0913; Executive Board Meeting Minutes, Dec 5, 1981; Affidavit, B. Harper, Esq., Feb 18, 1982, 1981, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Deposition, Jerry Brown, Secretary-Treasurer, National Union, Feb 18, 1982; "1199 News," Feb, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Phillips, Russell v. Lenox Hill Hospital & District 1199, 86 Civ. 1026 (RWS); Grievances 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - NLRB Correspondence, Jan 3, 1984; Correspondence, R. Phillips 14-Mar-84 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - American Arbitration Ass. (AAA), Transcript, pp. 1-181, Mar 21, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - AAA Transcript, pp. 182-363, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - AAA Transcript, pp. 364-544, Mar 21, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, R. Phillips, Mar 25, 1984; AAA Notice of Hearing, Oct 26, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, R. Phillips Jan 9 1985; Correspondence, R. Phillips Sept 18, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 82 Civ. / 86 Civ. 1026 (RWS); NLRB Charge, R. Phillips, Jan 27, 1986; Correspondence, R.P. to BH, with NLRB Charges (Dismissals) (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, R. Phillips to NLRB Apr 10, 1986; Correspondence from Defendant Hospital to Judge R.W. Sweet, Aug 5, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Note to B. Hall, Aug 17, 1986; AAA Opinion & Award, Dec 10, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Deposition, R. Phillips, pp. 1-184, Dec 10, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Defendant-Hospital's Request for Production, Dec 11, 1986; Deposition, R. Phillips, pp. 185-371, Dec 30, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Deposition & Subpoena, Andres Alfonso, Jan 7, 1987; Memorandum in Support of Hospital's Motion to Dismiss, Jan 20, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Deposition, R. Phillips, pp. 372-410, Jan 15, 1987; Deposition, with Corrections,Correspondence, Dec 9, 1986, 1986, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Hall to R.W. Sweet, Mar 23, 1987; Defendant Local 1199's 3(g) Statement of Facts, Mar 27 1987; Motion for Summary Judgment (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Affirmation with Exhibits, Mar 27, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Reply Memorandum in Support of Motion to Dismiss, Mar 30, 1987; Stipulation, Apr 29, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Affidavit, R. Phillips, pp. 1-42, with Exhibits, May 10, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Plaintiff's Memorandum in Opposition to 1199's Motion for Summary Judgment, May 12, 1987; Plaintiff's Rule 3 (g) Statements, May 13, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, July 8 1987; Amended Statement of Defendant 1199 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, BH, July 10, 1987; Settlement Stipulation, Feb 25, 1988, 1987, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - R. Phillips Employment Records, Notes, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Notes (Undated) (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Progressive Labor Party, Dec 19 1978; Flyers, Newsletters, Petitions, Nov., 1983; Undated Flyers, 1978, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Benin, Leigh, Vargas, Sam v. NYU Medical Center; NLRB Charge, Mar 24, 1972; NLRB Charge, Oct 11, 1979, 1972, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Puertas, Fred, 1199 / RWDSU v. NYU Medical Center; NLRB Charges 1982 -1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Subseries H: Unions (arrangement - alphabetical)
    - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF STATE, COUNTY & MUNICIPAL EMPLOYEES (AFSCME). District Council 1707; 1964, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - AFSCME - District Council 37; PLP / INCAR (Committee Against Racism), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TEACHERS (AFT); Zeluck, Steve; Executive Committee Meeting, Minutes, Nov 22 1968; Opinion & Order, Public Review Board, AFT, May 28 1971, 1968, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - UNITED FEDERATION OF TEACHERS (UFT); Loiacono, Charles, et. al., Arbitration Opinion & Award, NLRB Je 10 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - BAKERY & CONFECTIONARY UNION; Deposition, BH Oct 16 1961; Joint Appendix, Gartner, Robert v. Soloner, Jack, President, Local 492 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Local 50 (Bakery); Correspondence, Jan 27 1983; Grievance, Lynn Bell, July 5, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - BRICKLAYERS, MASONS & PLUMBERS UNION, Local #1, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - COMMUNICATION WORKERS OF AMERICA (CWA), Local 1101; Nabach, Joseph, Gilbert, Rusty, Kopp, Daniel v. New York Telephone Co. (Incomplete), undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - FEDERATION OF SPECIAL POLICE & LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICERS, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - HOTEL & RESTAURANT EMPLOYEES (HERE), Local 11, Chain Service; "Progress Bulletin," Local 11, Je 15, 1966; Complaint, Walgreen Eastern Co., Inc. v. James Gleason, Feb, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Local 11, Jan 2, 1968; Notice of Motion, Dec 18, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff's Motion for Preliminary Injunction; Correspondence, Je 25, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Appellee's Brief (BH, of Counsel); Memorandum in Support of Application to Intervene, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Feb 15 1972; Plaintiff's Memorandum of Law (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Plaintiff's Answer to Interrogatories, Oct 17, 1972; Affidavit in Opposition to Application for Adjournment (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Fred Ferrara Protests, New Politics, (BH) Summer, 1967; Correspondence to G. Schultz, Department of Labor (Election Protest), Mar, 1969, 1967, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Local 11 Documents - Constitution, Flyers, Newsletters (Originals), undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - HERE Local 164, Bartenders - Plattdeutche v. Local 164; Flyer Nov 6 1963; NLRB Stipulation Feb 10, 1965, 1963, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - HERE Local 6 - U.S. Court of Appeals Decision 1967, W. Wirtz, Secretary, Department of Labor v. Local 6 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - HERE Local 6 - Raccioppi, Joan v. Marriott Food Service, et. al., NLRB; Correspondence, Mar 11, 1981; Order July 30 1981 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - HERE Local 6 - Friend, Irene v. Crowing Cock National Restaurants, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Delmonico's Restaurant - Hendrix, Sharon, NLRB, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - HERE Local 100 - In Re Trusteeship 1984 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - INDEPENDENT ASSOCIATION OF PUBLISHERS' EMPLOYEES (IAPE); Frankland, Eric; Index No. 18406 / 81, Supreme Court of State of New York; Statement Aug 24 1981; Reply Memorandum in Opposition to Petition (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Memorandum in Support of Motion; IAPE Note with Job Listings, 25-Sep-86, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - INTERNATIONAL UNION OF ELECTRICAL WORKERS (IUE), Local 431, Genna, Guisseppe; NLRB 1983 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - INTERNATIONAL JEWELRY WORKERS UNION, Local No. 1; "Jewelry Worker Wildcats," Jan 20, 1972; Stipulation, Apr 3 1973, 1972, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - 73 Civ. 847 - (Jewelry); Memorandum in Opposition, Order for Judgment, July 16, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - AMALGAMATED LITHOGRAPHERS ASSOCIATION (ALA); Local No. 1 - Lithographers; 73 Civ. 3056; Loekle, Robert & Pike, William v. Swayduck, Edward, President, Local No. 1; Deposition, R. Loekle, pp. 1-59, Mar 22 1976; Defendant's Post-Trial Brief, 75 Civ. 3056 (WK), Oct 19, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Chronology of 1980 Election; Note to BH, R. Loekle, with Attachments; Correspondence, Minutes (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Dec 8, 1980; Meeting Transcript, pp. 1-58, Apr 1981, 1980, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Notice of Motion Sept 28 1981; Documents (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence & Stipulation, Oct 19, 1982; Answer, with Exhibits, Oct 27, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 82 Civ. 6425 (RLC); Order, Robert L. Carter, D.J., Oct 26, 1982; Stipulation, Mar 22, 1984, 1982, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Lithographers - Grievance, Lalama, F., 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - NATIONAL RURAL LETTER CARRIERS ASSOCIATION (NRLCA); Briggs, William v. Letter Carriers & U.S. Postal Service; Correspondence, Jan 27, 1986; Notice of Deposition (for), Dec 21, 1987, 1986, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, W. Sloan, Jan 7, 1988; Postal Service Documents (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 89-6275; Appellate Briefs; Petition for Rehearing (BH), undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS (BRAC); Includes "The Railway Clerk's Voice", undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - RETAIL, WHOLESALE DEPARTMENT STORE UNION (RWDSU), Local 1001, NLRB 1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Local 1102 - RWDSU; Woodberry, Warren (Discharge), 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Local 88 - RWDSU; Stewart, Edmund; NLRB - Mendon Leasing, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Local 88 - Mendon Leasing, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - SERVICE EMPLOYEES INTERNATIONAL UNION (SEIU), Local 144, Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home & Allied Health Services Union, SEIU; Easley, Charles v. Ottley, Peter J., President, Local 144, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Local 32 B - 32 J, SEIU; Whittaker, Cedric; NLRB - Columbia University, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - UPHOLSTERERS, DECORATORS & ALLIED CRAFTS, Local 44, Roman, Louis; 72 Civ. 4600; NLRB Correspondence, May 27, 1971; Complaint, Whitney North Seymour, Jr., U.S. Attorney, Oct 26, 1972; James D. Hodgson, Secretary, Department of Labor v. Local 44, Upholsterers (Title IV - L-MRDA), 1971, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Stipulation, Nov 17, 1972; Reply Affidavit, Dec 20, 1973, 1972, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Affidavit, BH, Jan, 1974; Affidavit, L. Roman, Oct, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 77 Civ. 0891 (CBM); Roman, L. v. United Exposition Service Co. Inc.; Index; Judicial Ruling, Charles M. Metzner, D.J., Dec 12, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Je 16, 1978; Correspondence, BH, Nov 29, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Feb 7, 1979; Correspondence, Oct 3, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Pre-Trial Order, Oct 5, 1979; Judicial Order (Metzner), Dec 5 1979 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission; (EEOC) Documents - L. Roman, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - New York State Division on Human Rights - Documents - L. Roman, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Joint Exhibits, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - UTILITY WORKERS OF AMERICA, Local 1-2; Correspondence, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Series III: Employment Discrimination
  Series III consists of legal files related to employment discrimination cases.
  - Canty, Seth (all), 1978-1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Pan Am Equities, Inc., 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Employment Discrimination Research File, 1977-1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Schifano, Charlotte, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Rhoda, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Watson, Jeptha B., 1982 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Librarian, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Series IV: Photographs
  The photographs include images of a 1962 protest in Times Square organized by the War Resisters League, portraits of Burton Hall, and a photograph of Paul Pisman after his assault.
  - Anti-Atomic Bomb Peace Demonstration (War Resisters League), March 1962 (Box A001, Folder 1)
  - Hall, Burton, 1979, undated (Box A001, Folder 2)
  - Pisman, Paul, circa 1961 (Box A001, Folder 3)
- Series V: 2007-2008 accretion
  Series V contains case files and legal documents including: affidavits, depositions, motions, District Court and appellate briefs, exhibits, appendices, court transcripts. Cases found in this series address various union disputes and date mostly from the late 1970s to the early 1990s. Major cases found in this series include The Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530; Drywall Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, Circle Industries, Component Assembly Systems, Inc., Bernie Wolff Construction, Co.; Petramale v. Local 17 & Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA); and Rodonich et. al. v. House Wreckers Union Local 95 of LIUNA, LIUNA, et. al.
  More detailed notes outlining the principal cases in this series and the types of documents in each casefile can be found in the detailed inventory on file.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Some materials (Box 39, Box 51A) have been moved to quarantine in July 2017 due to mold and may not be accessible to researchers.
  As of October 2017 Box 56 is missing.
  - Petramale v. Local 17 & LIUNA (LMRDA case), 1980s (Box 28)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CV-0337) (injunction case), 1984-1988 (Box 28)
  - Tapers Trustees (Local 1974) v. Component Assembly, 1980s (Box 28)
  - Petramale v. Local 17 & LIUNA, 1980s (Box 29)
  - Petramale v. Local 17 & LIUNA, 1980s-1993 (Box 30)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 81-CIV-0337, 1985-1991 (Box 31)
  - Drywall Tapers and Charles Long v. Operative Plasterers, 75-CV-4289, 78-7352 and 76-7108, 1970s (Box 31)
  - Alfarone v. Nastasi White, et al. (84-CIV-3181), 1984-1985 (Box 31)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1990 (Box 32)
  - Alfarone v. Nastasi White, et al. Case numbers 84-CIV-3181, 84-CIV-4028, 1978-1990 (Box 32)
  - De Rosa v. Blank, et al, 1970s (Box 32)
  - Improved Drywall v. Teamsters Local 272, 1984 (Box 32)
  - Mixed: early Drywall Tapers' Funds cases and jurisdictional dispute cases, circa 1990 (Box 33)
  - Alfarone v. Standard Drywall: Case # CV-81-015, circa 1990 (Box 34)
  - Alfarone, etc., et al. v. Nastasi White, etc., et al.: Case # 85-7899, 1979-2004 (Box 34)